真的有這麼明顯嗎？
Is it really that obvious?
我日日夜夜盯著你，因為
I've been eying you day and night, because
你看我的模樣，就是我想要的
you look at me the way I want you to
而每天我都，中、中、中，中你計
And every day I fall, fall, fall for you
我們用同一艘船
And we're in the same boat
從沒有到全都
from nothing to everything
這就是不同種的魔法
And it's a different kind of magic
不同種的人生體驗
A different kind of life to live
我們真的有區別？
Are we all that different?
真的沒區別？
Are we much the same?
還在尋找那個能夠修好我們的人
And we're looking for somepony to make us whole again
我知道你是我的星光
And I know that you're my Starlight
魔法在我身邊
The magic to all I am
請不要，問我過如何
Please don't ask how my day was
誠實會搞砸一切
Sincerity would fail me
還是喜歡把戲，拿下帽子就在
Still like to play tricks right outta the hat
你就別在意，讓我說說我到底什麼意思
Don't think about it, please just let me show you what I mean
每一天，我們都在找尋自我
Every day's a search for who we are
何時能喘口氣
When will we catch a break
並欣然接受自己？
And be happy with who we are?
這就是不同種的魔法
And it's a different kind of magic
不同種的人生體驗
A different kind of life to live
我們真的有區別？
Are we all that different?
真的沒區別？
Are we much the same?
還在尋找那個能夠修好我們的人
And we're looking for somepony to make us whole again
我知道你是我的星光
And I know that you're my Starlight
魔法在我身邊
The magic to all I am
這就是不同種的魔法
And it's a different kind of magic
不同種的人生體驗
A different kind of life to live
我們真的有區別？
Are we all that different?
真的沒區別？
Are we much the same?
還在尋找那個能夠修好我們的人...
And we're looking for somepony to make us whole again...